Vladislav Sinyavsky

Shanghai, China



sinyavsky.vladislav@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/vladislav-sinyavsky

Summary

As a front-end developer with over 4 years of experience in web development, I specialize in JavaScript, TypeScript, and popular frameworks such as React.js and Next.js. I have a deep understanding of Agile and Waterfall development methodologies and am well-versed in using React.js and Redux.

My focus is on creating clean, reusable, and maintainable code, adhering to industry best practices and web standards for an optimal user experience. I am a team player with strong communication skills and always eager to stay up-to-date with the latest technologies and industry trends.

Experience



Senior Frontend Developer

FatCoupon

Jun 2022 - Present (9 months)

Enhancing user experience and driving business growth through website redesign, development of new pages, and implementation of CI/CD pipeline.

My specific accomplishments include:

- Launched a new store page that increased conversions by 20%.
- Redesigned multiple sections on the company website, resulting in a 15% increase in user engagement.
- Developed traveled and gift card shop pages that generated additional revenue.
- Implemented a successful CI/CD pipeline, resulting in a 4x acceleration of production deploy time.
- Mentored new team members, providing guidance and training to help them become proficient in their roles and contribute to the success of the team.



Frontend Developer

FatCoupon

Jun 2020 - Present (2 years 9 months)

Delivering high-performance and user-friendly websites through innovative technologies and techniques.

Some of my significant contributions include:

- Designed and developed websites and admin panels using Next.js, TypeScript, React.js, Redux-Saga, Material-UI, and a large number of custom hooks.
- Researched and implemented emerging web technologies and trends to improve website performance by 3x and SEO indicators by more than 5x.
- Driven the development and redesign of FatCoupon.com, transforming it from a simple landing page to a million+ page shopping website.
- Improved UX/UI and followed best practices in redesigning the website.

Created hundreds of web connectors for the web extension and also created a unique algorithm for applying and stacking multiple discount coupons for an optimized shopping experience.

Frontend developer

Zabarankoy.by (ZBN)

Sep 2016 - Dec 2017 (1 year 4 months)

Developed SPA applications using Backbone.js and Marionette.js. Creation of new web modules and optimization of existing ones.

- Designed and developed user reviews and comments sections.
- Developed an admin interface.
- Expanding the functionality of the web modules, fixing bugs, and improving UX/UI.

Education



Henan University

Master's degree, Computer Software Engineering Sep 2018 - Dec 2021

Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

Bachelor's Degree, Faculty of Computer-Aided Design, Electronic technique and technology

Sep 2013 - Jun 2017

Skills

Next.js • React.js • JavaScript • TypeScript • Redux • Redux Thunk • Redux Saga • Material-UI • CSS • CSS3